Guide to the Tim Stevens Papers, 1945-2006 AIS.2006.11
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Tim Stevens Papers
1945-2006
1994-2004
ULS Archives & Special Collections
Stevens, Tim
AIS.2006.11
38 Linear Feet (26 boxes)
The collection documents the life and career of Tim Stevens, a prominent African American figure in the Pittsburgh community. Stevens served as president of the Pittsburgh branch of the NAACP (1994-2004) and was responsible for advocating for the rights of the African American community. This collection contains correspondence, meetings minutes, brochures, flyers, personal notes, news articles, memos, cassette tapes, VHS tapes and photographs.
Scope and Content Notes
The Tim Stevens Papers focus mainly on the period between 1994 and 2004 when Stevens served as President of the NAACP Pittsburgh branch. There is also material included on projects he initiated, particularly B-PEP and the Black and White Reunion. There are also personal materials, mainly concerning his career as a jazz vocalist and songwriter. The collection contains correspondence, news articles, memos, personal notes, meetings minutes, flyers, brochures, photographs, cassette tapes, compact discs, LPs and VHS tapes.
Previous Citation
Tim Stevens Papers, 1945-2006, AIS.2006.11, Archives Service Center, University of Pittsburgh
Biography
Timothy (Tim) Stevens was born in Pittsburgh, Pa., on May 4, 1945 to Georgetta and Jaspar Stevens. He was raised in the Hill District and attended the University of Pittsburgh, earning his Bachelor's Degree in Political Science in 1967 and his Master's Degree in Urban and Regional Planning in 1974.
In the wake of the 1968 assassination of Martin Luther King, Jr., Stevens decided to take a larger role in his community. In 1970, he became Executive Director of the Pittsburgh branch of the NAACP, holding this position for four years. In 1977, he began working as a volunteer coordinator at Mayview State Hospital. By 1990, he was made Director of Volunteer Resource Services, a position he currently holds. In 1986, Stevens founded the Black Political Empowerment Project (B-PEP), an organization aimed at promoting African American involvement in local, state, and national elections.
In November 1994, Stevens was elected President of the Pittsburgh branch of the NAACP. Over the next decade, Stevens would be continually re-elected to this position, being both praised and criticized for his very vocal presence in the media and his advocacy for African American rights and interests. Stevens took great interest in the tension between the African American community and the Pittsburgh Police Department. One of his projects, the Black and White Reunion, arose out of the controversial death of Jonny Gammage at the hands of the police. This project aimed to bridge tensions between the African American and Caucasian communities in Pittsburgh. Stevens lost the NAACP presidential election in late 2004, but left his mark on both the NAACP and the Pittsburgh community, where he still continues to be an active advocate for African Americans.
Stevens is also a well-known jazz performer and vocalist. He has written a variety of songs, including one recorded by Nancy Wilson. He has produced and released several albums, both solo and with his ensemble, the Tim Stevens Project. He also serves as a contributing editor for Pittsburgh Magazine's jazz section.
Arrangement
This collection in arranged into five series:
Series I. Black Political Empowerment Project (B-PEP), 1986-2004
Series II. Black and White Reunion, 1997-2005
Series III. NAACP, 1971-2006
Series IV. Personal, 1945-2003
Series V. Audio-Visual Material, 1950-2006
Access Restrictions
No restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Gift of Tim Stevens on June 6, 2006.
African American jazz musicians -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Police -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Politics; African Americans -- Civil rights -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Associations; Social action; Personal papers; Pittsburgh (Pa.); Economic development projects -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Pittsburgh (Pa.) -- Economic conditions; African Americans -- Political activity -- Pennsylvania -- Pittsburgh; Black Political Empowerment Project (B-PEP); National Association for the Advancement of Colored People. Pittsburgh Branch; Stevens, Tim; Pittsburgh (Pa.). Bureau of Police
- Black Political Empowerment Project (B-PEP), 1986-2004; I.
  Scope and Content Notes
  This series contains materials related to the Black Political Empowerment Project, known as B-PEP. This organization was founded by Stevens in the 1980s, and aimed to increase African American voting participation in the Pittsburgh community. This series contains correspondence, mailing lists, brochures, event information, and other documentation detailing B-PEP's activities throughout the 1980s, 1990s, and up to 2004.
  - Accountability Commission, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Accounting, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Acme Frame, undated (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Administrative Assistant, undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Agency Registration, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Agendas and Planning, 1995-2004 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Alleghenians, LTD., INC. Committee, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - A. Philip Randolph Institute, undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Artwork, 2000 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Awards, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Beyond Pittsburgh, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Bidwell Invoices, undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Billboards, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Billboards, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Billboards, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Billboards, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Black College Groups, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Black Leadership, undated (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Black Leadership Mailing List, undated (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Black MBAs, undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - "The Black Political Empowerment Project", undated (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Breakfast, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Bus Cards, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Bus Signs, 1991-1994 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Cabaret, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Campaign, 1990-1991 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Campaign, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Campaign, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Campaign for a New Tomorrow, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Candidates, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Candidates Community Forum, undated (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Chavis, Benjamin, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Church Registration, 1998 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Churches, 1986-1989 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - City/County, 1989-1990 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Clean Up Our Act, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Clean Up Our Act, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Clean Up Our Act, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Committee Members, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Communications, 1990-1993 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Communicators, 1993-1994 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Community Advisory Board, undated (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Community Celebration, 1994 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Community College of Allegheny County, 2003 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Community Service Award, undated (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - Consensus Building, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Contributors, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - County Council, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - Diary, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - DIGIT, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - District Election, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - District Elections, 1987-1993 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Donations, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Election, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Election Bureau, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - Election Calendar, 1999 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Election Day Rules, undated (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Endorsements, 1993 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - Equipment, undated (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - Expenses, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - Financial Family, undated (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - First Articles, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - "The First Year", 1987 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Fundraising Plan, undated (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Forums, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Funding, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 3-5)
  - General, 1986-1993 (Box 2, Folder 6-7)
  - General, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - General, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - General, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - General, 1999-2003 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Grants, 1995-1999 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Harrisburg, 1987 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Hatch Act, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - History, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Homer S. Brown Law Association, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Housing Authority, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Informer Articles, 1988-1990 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Initiative, 1986-1993 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Invoices, 1995 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - League of Women Voters, undated (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Legislation, 1989-1994 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Letterheads, undated (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Letters, 1986-1990 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Mailing Lists, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Mandela, Nelson, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Maps, undated (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Marketing, undated (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Mayoral Race, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - MacDonald, Valerie, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Media, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Media Packet, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Media Packet, 1991-1993 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Meetings, 1991-1993 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Meetings, 1999 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Membership, undated (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Memo, 1994 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Minutes, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Minutes, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Minutes, 1990-1991 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Minutes, 1992 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Minutes, 1993 (Box 2, Folder 42-43)
  - Minutes, 1993-1994 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Minutes, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Miscellaneous, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Monuments, 1993-1994 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Murphy, Tom, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - NAACP Political Action Committee, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - National Effort, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - New B-PEPers, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - New Initiatives, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - News Articles, 1988-1999 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - News Conferences, 1990-1994 (Box 3, Folder 10-11)
  - News Conferences, 1995-2004 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - News Releases, 1991-1993 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Notes, 1990-1993 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Notes, 1998-2003 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Operational Plans and Appendix, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Operational Plan, 1991-1997 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Operational Plan Changes, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Opinions, 1997 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Parliamentary Procedure, undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Petitions, undated (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Phase II, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Philosophy, undated (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Phone Bank, 1988-1994 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Pittsburgh Foundation, 1998-1999 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Pittsburgh Jazz Extravaganza, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Planning Council, 1987-1993 (Box 3, Folder 27-28)
  - Plaques, 1992-1993 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Political Manifesto, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Political Think Tank, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Poster Details, undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Project Vote, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Promotional Material, 1993-2003 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Proposal, 1995-1996 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Public Service Announcements, 1986-1992 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Quotes, undated (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Radio and Television, 1988-1990 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Rally, 1986-1988 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Registrars, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Registration, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Registration, undated (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Registration Centers, undated (Box 3, Folder 43-44)
  - Robinson, 1999 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - Schedule of Elections, undated (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - School Board, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - Self-Expression of Leadership, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 48)
  - Senior Citizens, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 49)
  - South Africa, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 50)
  - Statistics, 1986-1991 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Statistics, 1986-1994 (Box 4, Folder 2-3)
  - Statistics, 1993-1995 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Strategic Planning, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Strategy for Action, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Sweatshirts, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Sweatshirts, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Thank You Notes, undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Tickets, undated (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Transportation, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - United Steelworkers, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Urban League, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Vendors, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Video, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Volunteer Pool, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Volunteer Questionnaire, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Voter Weekend, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Voter Registration, 1992-1993 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Voter Registration Tips, undated (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - WAMO, 1986-1993 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Work Folder, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Workshop, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Y-PEP, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Y-PEP for B-PEP, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Y-PEP Proposal, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - 100% Club, 1986-1994 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - A+ Schools, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - A+ Schools, 2007 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - ACLU, 2007 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - ACORN, 2006-2007 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - Addresses, undated (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - African American Political Convention, 2005-2006 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - African American Leadership Conference, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - Agendas, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - Agendas, 2006-2008 (Box 33, Folder 9)
  - Allegheny COunty Democratic Committee, September 2013 (Box 33, Folder 10)
  - Allegheny County Jail and Prisoners' Rights, 2013 (Box 33, Folder 11)
  - Allegheny County DBE/MBE, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 12)
  - Annual Report, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 13)
  - Anti-Violence, 2006-2014 (Box 33, Folder 14)
  - Anti-Violence: Reprt of the Violence Prevention Task Force, 2012 (Box 33, Folder 15)
  - Black Elected Officials, undated (Box 33, Folder 16)
  - B-PEP, Spring 1991 (Box 33, Folder 17)
  - B-PEP, Spring 1991 (Box 33, Folder 18)
  - B-PEP, Spring 1992 (Box 33, Folder 19)
  - B-PEP, 1993 (Box 33, Folder 20)
  - B-PEP, Spring 1994 (Box 33, Folder 21)
  - B-PEP, Fall 1994 (Box 33, Folder 22)
  - B-PEP, 1994 (Box 33, Folder 23)
  - B-PEP, Spring 1995 (Box 33, Folder 24)
  - B-PEP, Summer 1995 (Box 33, Folder 25)
  - B-PEP, 1997 (Box 33, Folder 26)
  - B-PEP, 2002-2003 (Box 33, Folder 27)
  - Black Leadership Group, 2007 (Box 33, Folder 28)
  - Brother to Brother, 2007 (Box 33, Folder 29)
  - Brother to Brother Correspondences, 2007 (Box 33, Folder 30)
  - Campaign for Proficiency, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 31)
  - Campaign for Proficiency Retreat, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 32)
  - Campaign for Proficiency, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 33)
  - Campaign for Proficiency, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 34)
  - Campaign for Proficiency, 2007 (Box 33, Folder 35)
  - Casinos, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 36)
  - Casino Presentations, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 37)
  - Casinos, 2007-2008 (Box 33, Folder 38)
  - Carlisle, Twanda, 2005 (Box 33, Folder 39)
  - Carlisle, Twanda, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 40)
  - Cease Fire PA, September 2014 (Box 33, Folder 41)
  - Corporate Equity Inclusion Roundtable (CEIR), 2013 (Box 33, Folder 42)
  - Corporate Equity Inclusion Roundtable (CEIR), 2014 (Box 33, Folder 43)
  - Churches, 2004-2007 (Box 33, Folder 44)
  - CCAC Diversity Committe, 2008 (Box 33, Folder 45)
  - CCAC, 2006 (Box 33, Folder 46)
  - CCAC, 2007 (Box 33, Folder 47)
  - CCAC Diversity Audit, 2007 (Box 33, Folder 48)
  - CCAC Diversity and Equity Council, 2007 (Box 33, Folder 49)
  - CCAC and Coalition Against Violence, 2008 (Box 33, Folder 50)
  - Conference on Community Development Folder, July 2008 (Box 33, Item 1)
  - Citizen Police Review Board, 1995-2005 (Box 33, Folder 51)
  - Citizen Police Review Board, 2006-2015 (Box 33, Folder 52)
  - City County Merger, 2008 (Box 34, Folder 1)
  - City County Merger, 2009 (Box 34, Folder 2)
  - City Council, 2006-2012 (Box 34, Folder 3)
  - Clean Up Campaign, undated (Box 34, Folder 4)
  - Coalition Against Violence Resources, undated (Box 34, Folder 5)
  - Coalition Against Violence Community Manifesto, undated (Box 34, Folder 6)
  - Coalition Against Violence Community Services Directory and Strategies, undated (Box 34, Folder 7)
  - Coalition Against Violence Implementation Summary Report, 2008 (Box 34, Folder 8)
  - Coalition Against Violence Directory, 2007 (Box 34, Folder 9)
  - Coalition Against Violence, January 2007 (Box 34, Folder 10)
  - Coalition Against Violence, February 2007 (Box 34, Folder 11)
  - Coalition Against Violence, March-April 2007 (Box 34, Folder 12)
  - Coalition Against Violence, May 2007 (Box 34, Folder 13)
  - Coalition Against Violence, June 2007 (Box 34, Folder 14)
  - Coalition Against Violence, July-August 2007 (Box 34, Folder 15)
  - Coalition Against Violence, September-October 2007 (Box 34, Folder 16)
  - Coalition Against Violence, November-December 2007 (Box 34, Folder 17)
  - Coalition Against Violence, January, 2008 (Box 34, Folder 18)
  - Coalition Against Violence, January 2008 (Box 34, Folder 19)
  - Coalition Against Violence, January-February 2008 (Box 34, Folder 20)
  - Coalition Against Violence, March and May 2008 (Box 34, Folder 21)
  - Coalition Against Violence, June-July 2008 (Box 34, Folder 22)
  - Coalition Against Violence, August 2008 (Box 34, Folder 23)
  - Coalition Against Violence, September-December 2008 (Box 34, Folder 24)
  - Coalition Against Violence Even Planning, May-July 2008 (Box 34, Folder 25)
  - Coalition Against Violence Event, July 2008 (Box 34, Folder 26)
  - Coalition Against Violence, 2008-2009 (Box 34, Folder 27)
  - Coalition Against Violence, 2009 (Box 34, Folder 28)
  - Coalition Against Violence, 2010 (Box 34, Folder 29)
  - Coalition Against Violence, 2009-2012 (Box 34, Folder 30)
  - Coalition Against Violence Miscellaneous (Box 34, Folder 31)
  - Coalition Against Violence Valerie Dixon, July 2008 (Box 34, Folder 32)
  - Coalition Against Violence Reverend Sheldon Stoudemire, 2007-2008 (Box 34, Folder 33)
  - Coalition Against Violence Strategies (Box 34, Folder 34)
  - Coalition Against Violence Work File, 2007 (Box 34, Folder 35)
  - Coliseum, 2004-2005 (Box 34, Folder 36)
  - Coliseum, 2006-2007 (Box 34, Folder 37)
  - Communications, 2006 (Box 34, Folder 38)
  - Communications, January-March 2007 (Box 34, Folder 39)
  - Communications, April-May 2007 (Box 35, Folder 1)
  - Communications, June-August 2007 (Box 35, Folder 2)
  - Communications, September-December 2007 (Box 35, Folder 3)
  - Communications, 2008 (Box 35, Folder 4)
  - Community Calendar, 2006 (Box 35, Folder 5)
  - Community Development, 2007-2013 (Box 35, Folder 6)
  - Community Empowerment Association, 2007 (Box 35, Folder 7)
  - County Council, 2006-2008 (Box 35, Folder 8)
  - Council Members, undated (Box 35, Folder 9)
  - County Executive Meeting, October 2011 (Box 35, Folder 10)
  - CORO Center for Civic Leadership, 2006 (Box 35, Folder 11)
  - Darfur, 2006 (Box 35, Folder 12)
  - Death Penalty, 2005 (Box 35, Folder 13)
  - DBE/WBE, February 2007 (Box 35, Folder 14)
  - District Attorney, 2006 (Box 35, Folder 15)
  - Charles A. Dixon, 2005-2007 (Box 35, Folder 16)
  - DNA, 2005 (Box 35, Folder 17)
  - DNA Project, 2006 (Box 35, Folder 18)
  - DNA Task Force, 2006 (Box 35, Folder 19)
  - Dancing Demons, undated (Box 35, Folder 20)
  - Education, 2005 (Box 35, Folder 21)
  - Election, 2005-2006 (Box 35, Folder 22)
  - Election Protection, 2005-2007 (Box 35, Folder 23)
  - Election Protection, 2006 (Box 35, Folder 24)
  - Election Protection, 2006 (Box 35, Folder 25)
  - Election Results, 2005 (Box 35, Folder 26)
  - Email Action Network, 2006-2007 (Box 35, Folder 27)
  - EMS, April 2013 (Box 35, Folder 28)
  - Finances (Invoices), 2005-2007 (Box 35, Folder 29)
  - Finances/Funding, 2005-2014 (Box 35, Folder 30)
  - Forums, 2005 (Box 35, Folder 31)
  - Forums, January-March 2006 (Box 35, Folder 32)
  - Forums, April 2006 (Box 35, Folder 33)
  - Forums, May-December 2006 (Box 35, Folder 34)
  - Forums, January-February 2007 (Box 35, Folder 35)
  - Forums, March 2007 (Box 35, Folder 36)
  - Forums, April 2007 (Box 35, Folder 37)
  - Forums, 2010 (Box 35, Folder 38)
  - Jonny Gammage, 2005-2006 (Box 35, Folder 39)
  - Jonny Gammage Scholarship, 2008 (Box 35, Folder 40)
  - The Gathering, 2007 (Box 35, Folder 41)
  - Good Schools, 2006-2007 (Box 35, Folder 42)
  - GOTV Materials (Box 35, Folder 43)
  - Highlights, 2006 (Box 35, Folder 44)
  - Health Care Reform, 2005 (Box 35, Folder 45)
  - Health Care Reform, 2006 (Box 35, Folder 46)
  - Health Care Reform, 2006-2007 (Box 35, Folder 47)
  - Citizens Hearing on Health Care Reform, May 2006 (Box 35, Item 1)
  - House Bill 1243, October 2014 (Box 35, Folder 48)
  - House Bill 1318, September-November 2005 (Box 35, Folder 49)
  - House Bill 1318, December 2005-January 2006 (Box 35, Folder 50)
  - House Bill 1318, February 2006 (Box 35, Folder 51)
  - Hill District, 2007 (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Hill District Community Benefit Agreement, 2008 (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Hill District, 2009 (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Hill District One Hill, 2007-2008 (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Hill House, 2014 (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - History (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Incentives, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Imposed Blessing, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Jazz, 2006 (Box 36, Folder 9-13)
  - Jazz, 2007 (Box 36, Folder 14-17)
  - Jazz, 2008 (Box 36, Folder 18-20)
  - Jazz, 2009 (Box 36, Folder 21)
  - Jazz, 2013-2014 (Box 36, Folder 22)
  - Jazz Miscellaneous, 2005-2012 (Box 36, Folder 23)
  - Musicians, 2008 (Box 36, Folder 24)
  - Jerry Jackson Hearing, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 25)
  - Jerry Jackson, 2005-2006 (Box 36, Folder 26)
  - Judicial, 2006 (Box 36, Folder 27)
  - Landmark, 2007 (Box 36, Folder 28)
  - League of Young Voters (Box 36, Folder 29)
  - League of Women Voters, 2006-2007 (Box 36, Folder 30)
  - Last Chance For Power, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 31)
  - Lawton, Pamela, 2006-2007 (Box 36, Folder 32)
  - Letterhead, Undated (Box 36, Folder 33)
  - Mailed Communications, March 2005 (Box 36, Folder 34)
  - Mailed Communications, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 35)
  - Mailed Communications, 2005 (Box 36, Folder 36)
  - Mayor's Race, 2006-2007 (Box 36, Folder 37)
  - Mayor O'Connor, 2006 (Box 36, Folder 38)
  - Mayor Ravenstahl, 2007 (Box 36, Folder 39)
  - Mayor Ravenstahl, 2007 (Box 36, Folder 40)
  - M/W/DBE Advisory Committee, 2009 (Box 36, Folder 41)
  - M/W/DBE Advisory Committee Meeting, December 2005 (Box 36, Item 1)
  - M/W/DBE, 2006-2007 (Box 36, Folder 42)
  - M/W/DBE, 2005-2007 (Box 37, Folder 1)
  - M/W/DBE Advisory Committee Meeting, May 2006 (Box 37, Item 1)
  - Media, 2005-2008 (Box 37, Folder 2)
  - Media Contacts/Planning, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 3)
  - Meeting Information and Agendas, 2006-2007 (Box 37, Folder 4)
  - Minutes, August-December 2005 (Box 37, Folder 5-7)
  - Minutes, January-July 2006 (Box 37, Folder 8)
  - Minutes, August-December 2006 (Box 37, Folder 9)
  - Minutes, 2007 (Box 37, Folder 10)
  - Mission Statement (Box 37, Folder 11)
  - Moments, 2005 (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Myron Lewis, March 2006 (Box 37, Folder 13)
  - Name Tags, undated (Box 37, Folder 14)
  - National Coalition on Black Civic Participation, July 2008 (Box 37, Folder 15)
  - News Releases, February-August 2005 (Box 37, Folder 16)
  - News Releases, September-December 2005 (Box 37, Folder 17)
  - News Releases, January-May 2006 (Box 37, Folder 18)
  - News Releases, June-December 2006 (Box 37, Folder 19)
  - News Releases, 2007 (Box 37, Folder 20)
  - News Release, 2008 (Box 37, Folder 21)
  - Non-Profit File, 2014 (Box 37, Folder 22)
  - Oak Hill, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 23)
  - Oak Hill, 2006-2007 (Box 37, Folder 24)
  - Oak Hill: The Promise, 2003 (Box 37, Item 1)
  - Operational Plan, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 25)
  - Operational Plan Appendix, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 26)
  - Onorato, 2006 (Box 37, Folder 27)
  - Onorato, 2007 (Box 37, Folder 28)
  - Patrick, LeRoy, January 2006 (Box 37, Folder 29)
  - Peduto, 2014 (Box 37, Folder 30)
  - Pan Interfaith Impact Network, December 2006 (Box 37, Folder 31)